(Supported by NRTA's Online Audiovisual
Quality Creation & Distribution Project)
♪Black hair twines around bone♪
♪Night dew cold♪
♪Bronze mirror cracks
through three lifetimes♪
♪Shines on the sleepless♪
♪Yunmeng Marsh ebbs and flows♪
♪Vows sink deep♪
♪White-hair curse turns to snow♪
♪Covering the realm♪
=Reunion Across Time=
=Episode 9=
(Why can my blood)
(awaken the wickless Myriad Souls Lamp?)
(How did Song Ziyuan know)
(my blood is different from others'?)
(Who exactly)
(is my mother?)
My heart hurts so much.
Why does it hurt so much?
(Not good.)
(This will only make Chu Li
awaken the Chu Phoenix Call sooner.)
(Li,)
(I don't have much time left.)
(I have to find a way)
(to get you out of Jinan City soon.)
(30 Days Before the City Falls)
So, now,
have we completely swapped back?
If the lamp oil runs out,
I'm afraid...
It's fine.
My blood won't run dry anytime soon.
How can you...
I was kind enough to save you,
and you can't even say thanks?
All that blood wasted.
I just want him to come with me
to see my mother.
He should agree, right?
I wanted to ask... are you free?
I mean,
I want to go see my mother again.
But I'm afraid
Yun Hua will give me a hard time.
How about you come with me?
I have things to do.
Maybe another time.
Another time?
What's that supposed to mean?
I didn't do anything to offend him.
Chu Li,
you're no longer
part of our Shaman Clan.
You want to see the Grand Shaman?
Dream on.
Yun Hua,
did I dig up your family's graves
in a past life?
Do you have to hate me this much
in this life?
Don't try to provoke me.
Threats or sweet talk won't work on me.
It's useless.
(If I'd known,)
(I really should have dug up your
family's graves in my previous life.)
Chu Li.
How did you get hurt?
Let me put some medicine on it.
It must be hard to do it yourself.
Just a small wound. It's fine.
Does it hurt?
It's okay.
If you'd come with me
to the Shaman Clan today,
Would Yun Hua have dared
treat me like that?
Miss Chu Li,
I'm not obligated to stay by your side
and solve all your problems.
Song Ziyuan, you...
What's the meaning of this?
(Why is Song Ziyuan)
(so strange today?)
I'll be gentle.
Diviner Song? What brings you here?
What's going on with Diviner Song?
He seems to be in a bad mood.
Song Ziyuan,
did something happen to you?
Let go.
I have official matters to attend to.
Please don't disturb me, miss.
What's the matter with you?
You were fine just days ago.
Why the sudden change?
Did I offend you somehow?
No.
Song Ziyuan,
I hate guessing games.
Just say what you mean.
Get out.
Fine.
(Li,)
(I really am running out of time.)
What's wrong with Song Ziyuan?
Has someone put a curse on him?
Here, take the money.
Leave quickly.
Don't come back again.
I'm not leaving. Take your money back.
I'm telling you,
wherever Chu Li goes, I go.
- I said take it.
- I don't want it!
- Take it!
- Chu Li!
What's wrong?
He...
He told me
Diviner Song wants me
to leave this place
and never come back.
Why?
I don't know.
Maybe he's afraid I'll cling to you.
Shiqi,
why does Song Ziyuan
want to send Fusheng away?
I'll go talk to him.
Miss Chu Li, wait.
My master wants
you and Fusheng to leave together.
What?
Today,
I overheard Shiqi say
that someone invited Diviner Song
to a banquet
at Huancai Pavilion.
Where?
Huancai Pavilion.
Come on. Cheers.
Cheers.
Diviner Song, I heard
you took leave recently due to illness.
How is your health now?
Much better.
Good.
Diviner Song,
you rarely join us for drinks and music.
It's a great honor
to have you here today.
- Indeed.
- Let's drink.
- Another toast to you.
- Cheers.
Bottoms up.
♪Black hair twines around bone♪
♪Night dew cold♪
(Xizhao)
♪Bronze mirror cracks
through three lifetimes♪
♪Shines on the sleepless♪
♪Yunmeng Marsh ebbs and flows♪
♪Vows sink deep♪
♪White-hair curse turns to snow♪
♪Covering the realm♪
Diviner Song,
this is Huancai Pavilion's
most renowned beauty, Xizhao.
It's your first time here.
I suppose you haven't met her before.
Diviner Song, you're so handsome.
Why are you so afraid of me?
Chu Li, look.
Diviner Song really is here.
But Diviner Song is probably here
on official business.
I don't think
he's that debauched.
What's it to me?
Who are you?
We've booked the whole place today.
We...
We got the wrong place.
Sorry about that, Diviner Song.
We shouldn't have let them
spoil your evening.
Here, let me toast you again.
First comb,
to reach the netherworld.
Second comb,
the ghost paints its skin.
Third comb,
a wish becomes a prophecy.
Fourth comb,
steal heaven's will.
You will get what you desire.
Mercury veils Tianshu.
The Moon...
What comes after the Moon again?
This astrological verse
is so hard to memorize.
So annoying.
(Why have strange images)
(been flashing through my mind lately?)
(Could these be things
that will happen in the future?)
(Li!)
(How could this be the future?)
(Impossible.)
(That Song Ziyuan...)
(I just used the Myriad Souls Lamp
to restore his soul,)
(and he turned so cold right away.)
(As if he deserves my kindness.)
If you don't want me here,
I'll just leave.
So I won't be a bother.
Don't go.
You're drunk?
Stop laughing.
I'm going back.
What are you doing?
Li,
I'm so tired.
Are you crying?
Li,
what should I do?
What am I supposed to do?
♪You come treading through snow♪
Song Ziyuan,
what exactly
is the secret you're hiding?
Li,
when that sword went in,
did it hurt?
It hurt me too.
(I'm sorry.)
Chu Li?
What is it?
Before the night Yun Hua
made things difficult for me,
did you know me?
No.
No?
Song Ziyuan,
I have many ways
to make you tell the truth.
What do you want me to say?
In my previous life,
why did you kill me?
Your previous life?
Yes.
In my previous life,
I used the Chu Phoenix Call
to reverse time.
Don't tell me you don't know.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Then what did you mean last night?
I was drunk last night.
I don't remember.
Song Ziyuan,
don't think I wouldn't dare kill you.
♪Night rain falls in the courtyard,
shining on mortal partings♪
♪Strangers meet again,
past lives gleam in endless hues♪
♪A sharp arrow pierces memory♪
♪Longing spreads like dye♪
♪Beaded curtains
keep love and hate apart♪
♪Through boundless grief,
love remains hard to sever♪
♪A past bond, a parting dream;
when cold ends, purest joy remains♪
♪That year,
pear blossoms, verse, and laughter♪
♪One night, snow fell in wild flurries♪
♪All perfection in this world
hides regret♪
♪A drop of heart's blood seals love♪
♪No more longing enters dreams♪
♪When all turns to mist,
may you and I be safe forever♪
♪Through boundless grief,
love remains hard to sever♪
♪A past bond, a parting dream;
when cold ends, purest joy remains♪